<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Reading on darkvolumes</title>
    <link>https://darkvolumes.nz/reading/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Reading on darkvolumes</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 11:18:36 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://darkvolumes.nz/reading/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Metal is not noise</title>
      <link>https://darkvolumes.nz/reading/metal-is-not-noise/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Mar 2023 11:18:36 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://darkvolumes.nz/reading/metal-is-not-noise/</guid>
      <description>Metal is not noise The common perception of Metal as musical genre is of people screaming and making noise. Since I had to explain multiple times that there are Metal subgenres with clean vocals that can be appealing to a wider audience I thought it was worth a blog post.
The following are examples of metal songs with clean voice that you might be surprised to enjoy
Metal Ballads Sonata Arctica - Letter to Dana Sonata Arctica - Tallulah Ghost - Life Eternal &amp;ldquo;Opera Metal&amp;rdquo; / Nightwish Nightwish - Nemo Nightwish - Ghost Love Score Note that Tarja was the former lead vocalist of Nightwish.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Infographics</title>
      <link>https://darkvolumes.nz/reading/infographics/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 11:18:36 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://darkvolumes.nz/reading/infographics/</guid>
      <description>Infographics A collection of interesting infographics.
About Infographics d3 has a nice visual taxonomy of graphs, here is their example for maps.
Geo-Political Source: visualcapitalist.com</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Aphorisms</title>
      <link>https://darkvolumes.nz/reading/aphorisms/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2021 11:18:36 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://darkvolumes.nz/reading/aphorisms/</guid>
      <description>Aphorisms Biology enables, culture forbids - Yuval Noah Harari (Sapiens) Hackers read manuals - tweet Breakthroughs come from incremental progress - tweet </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>To the Rules of the World</title>
      <link>https://darkvolumes.nz/reading/to-the-rules-of-the-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2017 11:18:36 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://darkvolumes.nz/reading/to-the-rules-of-the-world/</guid>
      <description>To The Rulers Of The World CC: those adverse to them
I strongly despise this money-driven world. Money to have more power or power to have more money, I do not know, probably it is a vicious cycle. Interests, virtual money, this is one of the cancers of our world. I hate the fact the few pricks decide how much your life work is worth. I would like so much to leave for what a close friend of mine called “a small island of virtue” but there is no escape.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extracts  - Citizen Four</title>
      <link>https://darkvolumes.nz/reading/extracts-citizen-four/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1970 11:18:36 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://darkvolumes.nz/reading/extracts-citizen-four/</guid>
      <description>Extracts - Citizen Four Edward Snowden I remember what the Internet was like before it was being watched. And there has never been anything in the history of man like it. I mean you could have children from one part of the world having an equal discussion, where you know they were sort of granted the same respect for their ideas and conversation, with experts in the field from another part of the world on any topic, anywhere, anytime, all the time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Extracts - Phrack</title>
      <link>https://darkvolumes.nz/reading/extracts-phrack/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1970 11:18:36 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://darkvolumes.nz/reading/extracts-phrack/</guid>
      <description>Extracts - Phrack .:: The fall of hacker groups ::. Hacking is, in its very essence, an underground movement. Those who take part in it have always been the ones who (ab)used technology in ways beyond the knowledge of the larger userbase. It is tightly linked to intense efforts in unveiling previously unknown information as well as in sharing these discoveries.
We live in days of limited creativity. Moreover, as contraditory as it may seem, it looks particularly rare for creativity to arise from groups or teams.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
